

DOMINIK REMETEI

Web developer

=

Schodová 2, Brno Czech



+420 724087005



<u>drpoustevnik@gmail.com</u>

SKILLS

 REACT
 78%

 NODE
 70%

 CYPHER
 75%

 PYTHON
 85%

 GRAPHOL
 70%

SOCIAL



Facebook

facebook.com/doomrem



LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/domrem

ABOUT

I'm formally educated in Tourism and Marketing, having studied in Czech, France, and Denmark. I have an international working experience from academical as well as commercial environment. In the past 2 years I've transitioned to the world of web development starting with Python and currently JavaScript is my daily tool of choice

WORK EXPERIENCE

P

2019 - 2020

Web Developer

In 2019, I've moved to full-time development. I use various tools on a daily basis. Aside from the skills mentioned, I've worked with Docker, BaseX, Neo4j, Redis, various APIs and other management technologies, such as Mailchimp, Mandrill, HubSpot or Intercom.

P

2018 - 2019

Content Manager

I've started to collaborate with Engeto already in 2017. As content manager I've been improving the quality of various IT courses. I've got quite familiar with Git, Markdown, HTML5 and also CSS3. During these first two years I've had the opportunity to act as a python lecturer, python tester.

P

2016 - 2017

Product Development Intern

The dynamic environment of Philips HQ taught me how to navigate with a numerous group of people from different teams. As product developer, I had to analyze market data, online portfolio, suggest counteractions, coordinate various areas of multiple projects, drive product launches and more.

EDUCATION

2017 - 2019

